{
    "subject": "resource/Health_Service_Journal",
    "predicate": "property/publisher",
    "object": "resource/EMAP",
    "human_readable": "Health Service Journal was published by EMAP.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.874702513217926,
            "question": "Who published the Health Service Journal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7953048944473267,
            "question": "Does EMAP publish other types of journals besides the Health Service Journal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7103742361068726,
            "question": "When was the Health Service Journal first published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5624604821205139,
            "question": "What is the name of the publication company that produced the Health Service Journal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4933406114578247,
            "question": "What type of journal is the Health Service Journal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3936458230018616,
            "question": "What is the purpose of the Health Service Journal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2850477993488312,
            "question": "What topics does the Health Service Journal likely cover?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28415796160697937,
            "question": "Who might be the target audience for the Health Service Journal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20982296764850616,
            "question": "Where can I find more information about EMAP?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1667516529560089,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about EMAP?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Health Service Journal was published by EMAP.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3732_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I find more information about EMAP?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3732_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might be the target audience for the Health Service Journal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3732_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What topics does the Health Service Journal likely cover?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3732_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3732_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3732_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3732_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3732_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3732_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3732_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3732_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3732_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3732_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3732_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Health Service Journal was published by EMAP. The documents mention that \"Health Service Journal\" and \"hsj.co.uk are regularly read by over 100,000 decision-makers in healthcare and 92 per cent of health managers are readers on a monthly basis.\" and also provide the publication metadata for an article published in the Health Service Journal, which states that it was published by EMAP Publishing Ltd."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"Health Service Journal is a weekly news print title and website on the British National Health Service, healthcare management and health policy....Wikipedia\" and \"PublishesWeeklyFreebase OwnerEmap\". This confirms that Health Service Journal was published by EMAP."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}